{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Claudia is going camping with ___ girls.",
      "a": "three little other",
      "b": "little three other",
      "c": "little other three",
      "d": "three other little",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": ". \n- Adjective order: Opinion- size- age- shape-color- origin-material- purpose ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "21",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "How was your recent trip to Malaysia? \"It was great. We visited some temples, and spent the ___ days at the seaside.\"",
      "a": "last few sunny",
      "b": "few last sunny",
      "c": "few sunny last",
      "d": "last sunny few",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": ".\n- We often say \"the last/next few day (s)\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "21",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Peggy was so sleepy that she could hardly keep her eyes ___.",
      "a": "to be opened",
      "b": "open",
      "c": "opening",
      "d": "to open",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Keep sth + adj: remain status of something for sometime",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "21",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The tragedy sounds ___,",
      "a": "are true",
      "b": "to be true",
      "c": "TRUE",
      "d": "being true",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Verb of appearance: (feel, taste, smell, sound, look, appear, and seem)+ Adjective : modifies the noun before the verb ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "21",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "These tangerines taste ___,",
      "a": "well",
      "b": "good",
      "c": "to be well",
      "d": "to be good",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": ".\n- Verb of appearance: (feel, taste, smell, sound, look, appear, and seem)+ Adjective : modifies the noun before the verb",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "21",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ , I went to the railway station to see my friend off.",
      "a": "After my quickly finishing project",
      "b": "After finishing quickly my project",
      "c": "After finishing my quickly project",
      "d": "After finishing my project quickly",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- S + V + O + adj/adv",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "21",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will you give this message to Ms. Chen, please? \"Sorry, I can't. She ___.\"",
      "a": "doesn't any longer here work",
      "b": "doesn't any more work here",
      "c": "doesn't work here any longer",
      "d": "doesn't work any more here",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- No longer/not any longer: used when something used to happen or be true in the past but does not happen or is not true now",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "21",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can't you read? said Sandy ___ to the poster.",
      "a": "and point angrily",
      "b": "angrily pointing",
      "c": "and angrily pointing",
      "d": "angrily pointed",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Participle: \n+ Ing- form: do the action actively \n+ Ed- form: receive action from other",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "21",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I had _________, I'd visit Florida, stopping at all the small interesting places.",
      "a": "an enough long holiday",
      "b": "a long enough holiday",
      "c": "a long holiday enough",
      "d": "a holiday enough long",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n - Noun phrase: (a) adj + noun \n- Adj/adv + enough (for sbd) to do sth",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "21",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ to take this adventure course will certainly learn many useful skills.",
      "a": "Enough brave people",
      "b": "Brave enough people",
      "c": "People enough brave",
      "d": "People brave enough",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Adj/adv + enough (for sbd) to do sth \n- Enough + noun (for sbd) to do sth ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "21",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}